AN NGUYEN

Full Stack Developer

About me

As a research scientist, I have spent the last 10 years trying to develop cures for diseases afflict humans. I've always followed my passion and consequently I always aim for excellence in my career.

I am looking to apply my experience in project management, communication and critical thinking as a web developer. I readily tackle new challenges with grit determination, and a smile on my face.

I am an Australian Citizen with full rights to work in Australia.

Contact



annguyen@sydney.edu.au



github/pleathershaman



pleathershaman.github.io

Education

The Web Developer Bootcamp Udemy	2018 - 2019
The Modern React Bootcamp Udemy	2019 - 2019
Master of Science University of Sydney	2011 - 2012

Experience

Molecular Imaging Scientist

2012 - 2018

ANSTO

ANSTO is Australia's primary research facility for nuclear science. In this position, managed and contributed to research projects that use nuclear imaging. I was independently running multiple projects concurrently and was the main point of contact for all correspondence and communication. I was also responsible for organising project-related administration such as contracts, budgets, regulatory compliance and nondisclosure agreements.

Research Assistant

2008 - 2011

The Save Sight Institute

My main role in this position develop new experiments to investigate the causes of a rare eye disease. In this position, I set up a pipeline for analysing the differences in protein levels in a disease model.

Skills

HTML5	••••	css	••••
JavaScript	••••	Bootstrap	••••
React	••••	Redux	••••
Jest/Enzyme	• • • • •	Git/Github	••••
NodeJS	••••	MongoDB	••••
Problem Solving			
Project Mana	igement •		
Communicati	on •		

Awards

The Wenkart Foundation Grant
A competitive scholarship
valued at \$28,000 p.a. (AUD)
awarded for Master of Science.

References

Available on request

Personal Projects

AnBot Chatbot

AnBot is a chatbot powered by Google's Dialogflow that answers questions about its creator. Dialogflow takes in the users requests, runs its machine learning algorithm to best predict the users intent. Technologies used include, React, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6+ and Dialogflow for natural language processing.

Link: https://anbotchatbot.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/AnBot

Kitchen Catalogue

Kitchen Catalogue is an online database that allows users to create, edit and organise their cooking recipes. It features a full-stack MERN application with connection to a RESTful API, email confirmation and password reset. Technologies used include, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: http://kitchencatalogue.theaspiringwebdeveloper.com

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/KitchenCatalogue

Inspiration Montage

Inspiration Montage is a small react application that shows users a photo gallery based in their search terms. Featuring an infinite scroll and connection to the Unsplashed API, this program provides the user with visual inspiration on nearly every topic. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://inspirationmontage.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/InspirationMontage